Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - Academic issues records, 1995 - 2002; F-177-1-3; 97 cm of textual records
    - Research and external affairs records, 1995 - 2002; F-177-1-3-2; 56 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC research and external affairs activities. Activities, events and topics documented include TechBC's efforts to establish partnerships and links with various private corporations and the public sector, including various scientific and research institutes and councils, in order to develop TechBC's research and educational programs; participation in projects and other collaborative activities with these groups, including participation in forums and on boards; acquisition of funding to support the University's research activities; and the development of TechBC Corporation, an applied research company owned by TechBC and created to develop new technologies, incubate new companies, supply consulting services, and provide education to high tech companies. Records include reports, proposals, and business plans; correspondence; agreements; applications; presentations; booklets, brochures, and promotional material; annual reports; agendas; notes; and press releases.
      Technical University of British Columbia. TechBC Corporation
      - Advisory Council on Science and Technology, vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-1 (Archival box - standard 177-7)
      - Advisory Council on Science and Technology, vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-2 (Archival box - standard 177-7)
      - Applied Research Program, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-3-2-3 (Archival box - standard 177-7)
      - BC Biotech Alliance (BCBA), 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-3-2-4 (Archival box - standard 177-7)
      - BC Business Summit, 2000; F-177-1-3-2-5 (Archival box - standard 177-7)
      - BC Knowledge Development Fund (BCKDF), 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-6 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - British Columbia Technology Industries Association (BCTIA), 1999; F-177-1-3-2-7 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Canada research chairs, 2000 - 2002; F-177-1-3-2-8 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR), 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-10 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Canadian Strategic Software Consortium (CSSC), 1997; F-177-1-3-2-11 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Centre for Interactive Multimedia Research and Learning (CIMRL), 1998; F-177-1-3-2-12 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - CITec Network, vol. 1, 1996; F-177-1-3-2-13 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - CITec Network, vol. 2, 1996; F-177-1-3-2-14 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Community University Research Alliance Program (CURA), 1999; F-177-1-3-2-15 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Corporate education and training, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-3-2-16 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Credo Interactive Inc., 1998; F-177-1-3-2-17 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Demand Ventures Ltd., 1999; F-177-1-3-2-18 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Development activities, 2001; F-177-1-3-2-19 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
        Restricted in whole
      - DNA Productions Inc., 1999; F-177-1-3-2-20 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Granite Ridge Software, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-21 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - High Tech - general information, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-22 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Humanities and Social Sciences Federation of Canada (HSSFC), 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-3-2-23 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - IBM Canada, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-24 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - ISM-BC E-Commerce Learning Program, 2000; F-177-1-3-2-25 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - METL (Mastering Educational Technology and Learning), 1999; F-177-1-3-2-26 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Mosel Vitelic Semiconductor Manufacturing of Taiwan, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-27 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Motorola Canada Ltd., vol. 1, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-3-2-28 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Motorola Canada Ltd., vol. 2, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-3-2-29 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - National Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC), vol. 1, 1996 - 2002; F-177-1-3-2-30 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - National Science and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC), vol. 2, 1996 - 2002; F-177-1-3-2-31 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Networking breakfast, 1999/11/23, F-177-1-3-2-32 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - NewMIC (New Media Innovation Centre), vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-33 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - NewMIC (New Media Innovation Centre), vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-34 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Pangaea Ventures Ltd., vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-35 (Archival box - standard 177-8)
      - Pangaea Ventures Ltd., vol. 2, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-36 (Archival box - standard 177-9)
      - Pangaea Ventures Ltd., vol. 3, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-37 (Archival box - standard 177-9)
      - Potential partners, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-3-2-38 (Archival box - standard 177-9)
      - Principals of Educational Partnerships [MAETT report], 1999; F-177-1-3-2-39 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Prototype Development Program (PDP), 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-40 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Research and External Affairs ADVANCE 2000/11/10, F-177-1-3-2-41 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Research Cluster on Educational Technology and Policy, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-42 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Research seminars, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-43 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Ross Mitchell / Broadcom, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-44 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Science Council of BC, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-3-2-45 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC), vol. 1, 1995 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-46 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC), vol. 2, 1995 - 2000; F-177-1-3-2-47 (Archival box - standard 177-10)
      - TechBC Corporation, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-48 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
        Restricted in part
      - TechBC Corporation, vol. 2, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-49 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TechBC Corporation, vol. 3, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-50 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TechBC Corporation, vol. 4, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-51 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TechBC Corporation Board meeting, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-52 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TechBC Corporation Board of Directors, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-53 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TechBC Corp Board meeting, 2000/11/15, F-177-1-3-2-54 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TeleLearning - NCE, vol. 1, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-3-2-55 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - TeleLearning - NCE, vol. 2, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-3-2-56 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - Telemedia, 1998; F-177-1-3-2-57 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - Then/Else: Interactivity Research Centre, 2000; F-177-1-3-2-58 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - University/industry/research liaison, 1999; F-177-1-3-2-59 (Archival box - standard 177-11)
      - Western Research Network on Education and Training, 1996; F-177-1-3-2-60 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - WestMOST, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-3-2-61 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
  - Administration records, 1990 - 2002; F-177-1-4; 1.16 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the general administration of the University and the development of its programs, services, and physical presence. Records include correspondence; reports, position papers, briefs, and working papers; minutes, terms of reference, and supporting papers; agreements; financial reports; promotional material; architectural drawings; legislation; lists; and reference material.
    - Administration - general records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-4-1; 10 cm of textual records
      Sub-series consists of records relating to the administration of TechBC. Activities, events and topics documented include the planning and establishment of the University and its services; the goals, mission and values of the University; its economic mandate; official university committees; and university history. Includes minutes of the Priorities Implementation Group and some records relating to the University Ethics Research Committee and the Knowledge Assets Management Sub-group. Records include correpondence; minutes, terms of reference and supporting papers; reports, position papers, and briefs; legislation; lists; and reference material.
      Technical University of British Columbia. Priorities Implementation Group; Technical University of British Columbia. University Ethics Research Committee; Technical University of British Columbia. Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee. Knowledge Assets Management Sub-group
      - Economic mandate - general, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-4-1-1 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - History of TechBC, 1998; F-177-1-4-1-2 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Knowledge management, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-4-1-3 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Memberships/subscriptions, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-4-1-4 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Mission/purpose/values, 1995; F-177-1-4-1-5 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - PORTAL (library), 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-1-6 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - PORTAL resource update, 27 July 1999 - 1999; F-177-1-4-1-7 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Priorities Implementation Group (PIG), 1999; F-177-1-4-1-8 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - TechBC Act, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-4-1-9 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Technical University of British Columbia Act, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-4-1-10 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - United Way 2000 campaign, F-177-1-4-1-11 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - University Act, 1999; F-177-1-4-1-12 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - University committees, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-1-13 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
    - Campus development records, 1990 - 2002; F-177-1-4-2; 1.07 m of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to the determination and development of a permanent location for the University. Activities, events and topics documented include temporary accommodation arrangements; the consideration of various sites; negotiations with the Provincial government for a permanent location; negotiations with the Insurance Corporation of British Columbia (ICBC) for the Surrey City Central site; the design of and acquisition of funds for the building at the City Central site; and the development of a facilities program for the City Central campus. Records include correspondence; reports, briefs, and working papers; minutes and supporting papers; agreements; financial reports; promotional material; and architectural drawings.
      The material was arranged according to the original filing system of the creator. Files are mainly arranged alphabetically.
      - Bing Thom Architects, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-1 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Bing Thom Architects, vol. 2, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-2 (Archival box - standard 177-12)
      - Bing Thom Architects, vol. 3, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-3 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Bing Thom Architects, vol. 4, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-4 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Bing Thom Architects, vol. 5, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-5 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Central City - March 25, 2001 event, F-177-1-4-2-6 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - The cradle, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-4-2-7 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Education Technology and Learning Complex, 1999; F-177-1-4-2-8 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Filing (site files) [ICBC/TechBC partnership], probably duplicates, 1998; F-177-1-4-2-9 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Furniture and equipment, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-10 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd., vol. 1, 1999 - 2002; F-177-1-4-2-11 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd., vol. 2, 1999 - 2002; F-177-1-4-2-12 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - King George Park site, 1997; F-177-1-4-2-13 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Leased space - various options, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-14 (Archival box - standard 177-13)
      - Leased space - various options, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-15 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Leased space - various options, vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-16 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Leased space - various options, vol. 4, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-17 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Preliminary facilities program, 1999; F-177-1-4-2-18 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Project managers (general), 2000; F-177-1-4-2-19 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Project One Steering Committee, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-20 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Research centre, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-4-2-21 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Station Tower, 1996; F-177-1-4-2-22 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - TechBC draft documents, vol. 1, 13 January 2000 - January 2000; F-177-1-4-2-23 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - TechBC draft documents, vol. 2, 13 January 2000 - January 2000; F-177-1-4-2-24 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - TechBC draft documents, vol. 3, 13 January 2000 - January 2000; F-177-1-4-2-25 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #10, vol. 1, 1 July 2000 - 20 November 2001; F-177-1-4-2-26 (Archival box - standard 177-14)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #10, vol. 2, 2 July 2000 - 20 November 2001; F-177-1-4-2-27 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #9, vol. 1, 1 March 2000 - 3 June 2000; F-177-1-4-2-28 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #9, vol. 2, 1 March 2000 - 3 June 2000; F-177-1-4-2-29 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #9, vol. 3, 1 March 2000 - 3 June 2000; F-177-1-4-2-30 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #9, vol. 4, 1 March 2000 - 3 June 2000; F-177-1-4-2-31 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #8, vol. 1, 1 January 2000 - 29 February 2000; F-177-1-4-2-32 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #8, vol. 2, 1 January 2000 - 29 February 2000; F-177-1-4-2-33 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #8, vol. 3, 1 January 2000 - 29 February 2000; F-177-1-4-2-34 (Archival box - standard 177-15)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #7, vol. 1, 1 October 1999 - 31 December 1999; F-177-1-4-2-35 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #7, vol. 2, 1 October 1999 - 31 December 1999; F-177-1-4-2-36 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #7, vol. 3, 1 October 1999 - 31 December 1999; F-177-1-4-2-37 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #6, vol. 1, 1 August 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-38 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #6, vol. 2, 1 August 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-39 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #6, vol. 3, 1 August 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-40 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #6, vol. 4, 1 August 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-41 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #5, vol. 1, 1 June 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-42 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #5, vol. 2, 1 June 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-43 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #5, vol. 3, 1 June 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-44 (Archival box - standard 177-16)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #5, vol. 4, 1 June 1999 - 30 September 1999; F-177-1-4-2-45 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #4, vol. 1, 1 March 1999 - 31 May 1999; F-177-1-4-2-46 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #4, vol. 2, 1 March 1999 - 31 May 1999; F-177-1-4-2-47 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #4, vol. 3, 1 March 1999 - 31 May 1999; F-177-1-4-2-48 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #4, vol. 4, 1 March 1999 - 31 May 1999; F-177-1-4-2-49 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #3, vol. 1, 1 January 1999 - 28 February 1999; F-177-1-4-2-50 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #3, vol. 2, 1 January 1999 - 28 February 1999; F-177-1-4-2-51 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #3, vol. 3, 1 January 1999 - 28 February 1999; F-177-1-4-2-52 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #2, vol. 1, 1 September 1998 - 31 December 1998; F-177-1-4-2-53 (Archival box - standard 177-17)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #2, vol. 2, 1 September 1998 - 31 December 1998; F-177-1-4-2-54 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #2, vol. 3, 1 September 1998 - 31 December 1998; F-177-1-4-2-55 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #2, vol. 4, 1 September 1998 - 31 December 1998; F-177-1-4-2-56 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #2, vol. 5, 1 September 1998 - 31 December 1998; F-177-1-4-2-57 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #1, vol. 1, 1 January 1998 - 31 August 1998; F-177-1-4-2-58 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #1, vol. 2, 1 January 1998 - 31 August 1998; F-177-1-4-2-59 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #1, vol. 3, 1 January 1998 - 31 August 1998; F-177-1-4-2-60 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Surrey City Centre site file #1, vol. 4, 1 January 1998 - 31 August 1998; F-177-1-4-2-61 (Archival box - standard 177-18)
      - Site development, vol. 1, 1990 - 31 December 1997; F-177-1-4-2-62 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Site development, vol. 2, 1990 - 31 December 1997; F-177-1-4-2-63 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Site development, vol. 3, 1990 - 31 December 1997; F-177-1-4-2-64 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre Mall Ltd., 2000; F-177-1-4-2-65 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, vol. 1, 10 March 2000; F-177-1-4-2-66 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, vol. 2, 10 March 2000; F-177-1-4-2-67 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, vol. 3, 10 March 2000; F-177-1-4-2-68 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, vol. 4, 10 March 2000; F-177-1-4-2-69 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, vol. 5, 10 March 2000; F-177-1-4-2-70 (Archival box - standard 177-19)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-71 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-72 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-73 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-74 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, with associated documents [Bernie's copy], vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-75 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC proposal to create an urban facility for TechBC - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999, with associated documents [Bernie's copy], vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-76 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - Surrey City Centre - space review and value analysis, 2000; F-177-1-4-2-77 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - Technical University of British Columbia - Interim Planning Council: preliminary report…(working copy #1, peer review), June 1996; F-177-1-4-2-78 (Archival box - standard 177-20)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. and Technical University of British Columbia - Surrey City Centre - signed original, vol. 1, 2000; F-177-1-4-2-79 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. and Technical University of British Columbia - Surrey City Centre - signed original, vol. 2, 2000; F-177-1-4-2-80 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. and Technical University of British Columbia - Surrey City Centre - signed original, vol. 3, 2000; F-177-1-4-2-81 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. Board - working file, B. Sheehan, vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-82 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. Board - working file, B. Sheehan, vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-4-2-83 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
      - ICBC Properties Ltd. Board -meetings, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-4-2-84 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
  - Community relations records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-5; Analog originals: 12 cm of textual records 2 moving images (2 videocassettes) Digitized materials: Preservation copies - 2 mov files (5.94 GB) Access copies - 2 mp4 files (123.7 MB)
    Sub-series consists of records relating to community and public relations activities of the University and its Community Relations Department. Activities, events and topics documented include community relations and awareness, including participation in community events and activities, media relations, communications strategies, campus development, special events, and student recruitment. Records include press releases and newspaper articles; promotional material; interviews, speeches, and presentations; reports; videos; and photographs.
    Technical University of British Columbia. Community Relations Department
    Analog originals were digitized by the Archives in September 2018. Digitial copies are available in mp4 (access format) and mov (preservation format) for all moving images in this series. Please contact the reference archivist to request copies.
    - Advertising - newspaper, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Communications plan, 18 June 1996; F-177-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Community relations - general, vol. 1, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Community relations - general, vol. 2, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - First Nations [Aboriginal Advisory Group to TechBC], 1999; F-177-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Innovation (general), 2001; F-177-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Media relations, 9 December 1999; F-177-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-21)